Guide to the Papers of Peter Koch, 1974-2003 M1584
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Peter Rutledge Koch papers
1975-2006
M1584
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
157.0 Linear feet
Papers of find press printer, Peter Koch, include press proofs, correspondence, teaching files, sales and financial material, student work, job files and media.
Koch, Peter Rutledge
Access:
Collection is open for research to boxes listed in Container listing; Project files are in process and not yet available.
Related Archival Materials note
Peter Koch's hard drive has been processed separately; please see M.1584.Media.
Biography
Peter Rutledge Koch has been designing and printing books and ephemera since 1974, beginning his career in Missoula, Montana with one platen press. He since settled in the San Francisco Bay area and following the San Francisco literary tradition of fine press printing, has acquired an international reputation and several more presses. His clients and collectors range from major international research libraries to bibliophilic organizations and private collectors and publishers. Between commissions, he designs, prints and publishes limited editions of ancient Greek philosophers, the musings of maverick poets, and the images of world-renowned wood engravers and photographers. Editions Koch specializes in publishing limited edition livres d'artiste, broadsides, portfolios, and text transmission objects.
His works have previously carried the imprints: Black Stone Press, Peter Koch, Printer, and Hormone Derange Editions.
When not working in his studio, he teaches the history of typographic design and printing on the Albion hand press at the University of California, Berkeley's Bancroft Library Press.
[From the website: http://www.peterkochprinters.com/index.php]
Scope and Content of Collection
The Peter Koch Papers contain correspondence, project files (proofs, plans, templates, etc.), manuscripts, sales records, student projects, etc.
It is arranged in 14 series:
General files
Teaching files
Financial
Job files
Correspondence, alphabetical
Correspondence, miscellaneous
Media
Datebooks, planners, etc.
Reviews, awards, Roxburgh Club
Book sales
Poems Essays About Koch
Dirk Lee Archive
Student Projects
Book archives
Bancroft Library. Friends; Black Stone Press.; Book Club of California.; Gleeson Library Associates.; Koch, Peter Rutledge; Phillips, Matt, 1927-; Press in Tuscany Alley.; Roxburghe Club of San Francisco.; San Francisco Public Library; Fine press; Fine printing--20th century; Fine printing--California; Fine printing--San Francisco, Calif.; Printing--U.S.
- Series I. GENERAL FILES
  General note
  Arranged chronologically backwards.
  - 2000: Bloody Murder/Bancroft, #1108; Semo Sciopai, #1112 (Carton 3)
  - 1999: GLA Spring Keepsake, #1056 (Carton 3)
  - 1998: "The Music of Healing"-Tommy Sands Peter Seeger, #975; GLA Annual Meeting Program, #983; Wm. Stewart, #1050 (Carton 3)
  - 1997: Wilhelm Wedding, #1114; Veiled Histories Book, Allen Staff File, #1120 (Carton 3)
  - 1993: Book Club of California Quarterly, #531; Holtzman Birth Announcement and EP, # 532; "The Sparrow" Broadside, Ann Kyle-Brown, #536; "This One" Bradside, Ann Kyle-Brown, # 538; "The Common Man" Broadside, Ann Kyle-Brown, #537; Rosburghe Club, "Borden Burden" Keepsake, # 543; USF Darwin Symposium Announcement, #546; "Printer" Sephanie Marlis Broadside, #547 (Carton 4)
  - 1993: GLA Christmas Card, #493; GLA Donohue Rare Book Rm. Announcement, #505; Roxburghe/ Zamorano Clubs Keepsake, #509; Roxburghe/ Zamorano Clubs Menu, #517; Friends of Bancroft Library Annual Meeting Keepsake, # 519; "Second Thoughts"-William T. Wiley Michael Hannon, # 527 (Carton 4)
  - 1991: Schlegal Christmas Card and EP; #450; Hormone Derange Broadsides: Raven Brought the Light"; #451; GLA Brochure; #471; "The Living Pan" broadside - Mayacamas Press; #476; "The Johnson Family of Hyde Park and Sag Harbor" - Albert Southwick; #479 (Carton 1)
  - 1990: "Favorite Songs" Michael Rothenberge Big Bridge Press; # 420; New College Catalog; #432; "Under Two Civilizations" - Tarnow Baron Stanford; #433 (Carton 1)
  - 1989: Poetry and Revolution Catalog; # 365; Mondavi Stationery; #368; Chloris Nobel Earthquake Book; # 374 (Carton 1)
  - 1988: Getty Center Scholars Poster; #340; Museum of Modern Art Wine Label (Manwaring Design); #355 (Carton 1)
  - 1987: Pier 45 Logo Cards; #287; GLA Christmas Card; #294; CCAC Travel Brochure and EP; #311; Kessel-Torrano Wedding Announcement; #312; Aid and Comfort Invitation; #313; MFK Fischer Broadside: Aid comfort Portfolio Contribution; #314; Kenter Canyon Farms Business Cards;#317; Daedalus Conservation and Framing: Promo Brochure and EPS; #324; Corn off the Cob; #325; Gary Snyder Poem/ Mundy port; #248; Bakers of Paris Christmas Card; #249; Garden Salad Stickers; #255 (Carton 1)
  - 1986: Off the Beaten Path Stationery/Letterhead, #258; Jim Jennings sign, #259; Directory of Berkeley booksellers, #260; Mason-Hugel Wedding, #267; Hawaiian/Californian Act Keepsake Roxburghe Club, #271; Pia Pizo exhibit announcement, #272; "Apology for Bad Dreams", Robinson-Jeffers/ Mundy-Linden Book and Announcement, #273; Barbara Parsons Prints, #275; Dear Doctor: C. Odegaard- Kaiser Family Foundation, #285; "After Paradise" Czeslaw Milosc for Black Oak Books, # 286 (Carton 2)
  - 1985: Eliot Holtzman Photography Price List, Portfolio Specialist Brochure, #209; Eliot Holtzman BUSINESS CARDS, #205; Bancroft Library, "Europeans The Making of Modern California", #227; International Association of Bibliophiles, #230; S.F. State, Friends of Leonard Lib., # 232; Taylor and Taylor, James Elliot, #235 (Carton 2)
  - 1984: Read Aloud Rhymes, E.H. Severson, #169; Jennings and Stout Season's Greeting Card, # 170; "The Garden", R. Pinsky for Black Oak Books, # 171; Photographs 1975-1980: Joel D. Levinson, #174; Karen Gorden Broadside, Black Oak Books, # 172; A Tribute to Bozz Scaggs-Molly Gleason Broadside, #175; Book Club of California, Mosley Lecture, # 176; Black Oak Three Penny Review Tribute, # 177; GLA Spring Tour Announcement-J. London Country, # 178; Arts and Books, G.B. Carson Business Card, #180; GLA Camera Ready, # 181; GLA Spring Tour # 182; GLA Autumn Meeting Announcement, # 163; GLA Autumn Meeting Program, # 184; GLA Christmas Card, # 185; Stationery and EP- Clyde Winters Annie E. Maass, #187; Lonnie Graham/Debora Lewis, #188; Drew Nadell/ Herrick-Rosburghe Club Keepsake (Typography Broadside), #189 (Carton 2)
  - 1984: Read Aloud Rhymes, E. H. Severson, Illustrated by Mary Stent, # 190; "It's Just the Truth" Howard A. Friedman Book, #202 (Carton 3)
- Series II. TEACHING FILES
  Note:
  Listing generated from creator's folder title and entered by student assistants.
  - Promotional Material for P. Koch Courses; #1154 (Carton 5)
  - Texas PBI; #1411 (Carton 5)
  - Surrealist Project: Class at Education Liberation From, U.C. Berkeley (1972); # 1156 (Carton 5)
  - UC class: Bancroft Library class 2002 (Carton 5)
  - Syllabus and Bibliography, 2004-2005 (Carton 5)
  - U.C. Class Department of History (2004) (Carton 5)
  - History 2004-2005 (Carton 5)
  - KALA Class: "Introduction to Letterpress" Spring 1989 (Carton 5)
  - Press at Tuscany Alley; includes correspondence, grant and other fundraising material, San Francisco State University class materials, etc.
    - San Francisco State University Berliner Type Order- Tuscany Alley (1991) (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Class- Spring 1990; #913 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Class Spring 1990, #914 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Fall 1990; # 915 (Carton 5)
    - Letters from Joyce Wilson (Mrs. Adrian Wilson) for Estab. Press in Tuscany Alley (1990); #916 (Carton 5)
    - Fundraising Press at Tuscany Alley (1991); # 917 (Carton 5)
    - Tuscany Alley Correspondence-P.K B. Foster (1991); # 918 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Spring 1991- "Book as Object"; # 919 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Spring 1991 Class- Tuscany Alley; # 920 (Carton 5)
    - Correspondence regarding funding - Tuscany Alley (1991); #921 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Fall 1991 Class - T. Alley; #922 (Carton 5)
    - Tuscany Alley- Printing of Notebook Poems by Robert Duncca, drawings by Jess (1991); #923 (Carton 5)
    - Haas Foundation Grant - Tuscany Alley (1991); #924 (Carton 5)
    - L.E.F. Foundation Grant - Tuscany Alley (1991); # 925 (Carton 5)
    - Proposal for Press at Tuscany Alley (1991); #926 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Fall 1992- Tuscany Alley; # 927 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Spring 1992 Class- Tuscany Alley; #928 (Carton 5)
    - L.E.F. Foundation: Tuscany Alley 1992; #929 (Carton 5)
    - Tamarack Foundation Grant Request- Tuscany Alley 1992; #930 (Carton 5)
    - Grants Received Summaries-Tuscany Alley 1992; #931 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Spring 1993 Class- Tuscany Alley; #933 (Carton 5)
    - Other Grant Requests; "My Tin Cup Text"- Tuscany Alley 1992; #932 (Carton 5)
    - Receipts/Unpaid- Tuscany Alley 1993; #934 (Carton 5)
    - Letters Requesting Donations- Tuscany Alley 1993; #935 (Carton 5)
    - S.F. Foundation (Received Progress Reports $1,000 grant)- Tuscany Alley 1993; #936 (Carton 5)
    - Watermark- Tuscany Alley 1993; #937 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Class- "Word into Print"- Tuscany Alley 1993; #938 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Class- "Word into Print"- Tuscany Alley 1993; #939 (Carton 5)
    - San Francisco State University Design Foundation- Tuscany Alley 1993; #940 (Carton 5)
    - Correspondence w/ Nancy McDermid- Tuscany Alley 1993; #941 (Carton 5)
    - Haas Foundation- Tuscany Alley 1993; #942 (Carton 5)
    - Miscellaneous Letters RE: Tuscany Alley 1993; #943 (Carton 5)
    - Receipts and Invoices- Tuscany Alley 1993; #944 (Carton 5)
    - Ann Kyle Brown: Development Strategy- Tuscany Alley 1993; #945 (Carton 5)
    - Proposed Merger Between Tuscany Alley and San Francisco Center for Book 1993; #946 (Carton 5)
    - Tuscany Alley students and books (Carton 5)
    - Sales of Robert Duncan Book Notebook Poems (produced at Tuscany Alley) 1994; #947 (Carton 5)
  - Correspondence w/ Sid Berger RE: Teaching Materials 1994; #949 (Carton 5)
  - Book Design Foundation Letters RE: funding (previously Adrian Wilsons) 1994; #951 (Carton 5)
  - San Francisco State University Class "The Book as Artifact" 1994; #951 (Carton 5)
  - Univ. of Montana Class: "The Art of the Book: An Intro to Fine Printing Design." 1997; #952 (Carton 5)
  - Teaching Files- Mendicino Art Center 1985-87; #953 (Carton 5)
  - New College: Establishing Press Book Arts Program -1989; #954 (Carton 5)
  - HRC- Texas PBI #1405 (Carton 5)
  - New College Class: "The Book as Object" 1989; #955 (Carton 5)
  - New College Class 1990; #956 (Carton 5)
  - KALA Class 1990; #957 (Carton 5)
  - UC Class: [ Bancroft Library] "The Hand Printed Book in its Historical Context" 1992; #958 (Carton 5)
  - UC Class: Bancroft Library "The Hand Printed Book in its Historical Context" 1993; #959 (Carton 5)
  - UC Class: Bancroft Library "The Hand Printed Book in its Historical Context" 1994; #960 (Carton 5)
  - Course Proposals- Various Years; #1158 (Carton 5)
  - Shelly Hoyt- Resume and Class outline; #1400 (Carton 5)
  - Mayory[?] Cantors Outline; #1402 (Carton 5)
- Series III. FINANCIAL
  Includes invoices, check registers, and receipts.
  - Check Register, 12/15/1976-12/71977; 12/1977-3/1981; 1981-1984; 1984-1985; 1990-1998; 1982-1990 (Carton 6)
  - Check book records, 1983; 1992-1996? (Carton 6)
  - Payment Record, 7/1985-12/1985; 1/2/1986-12/24/1986; 12/1986-9/1987; 9/1987-7/1988; 7/1988-12/1988; 1/1989-7/1989; 7/1989-6/1990; 6/1990-12/1990 (Carton 6)
  - Register, 1/1991-10/1991; 10/1991-12/1991; 1/1992-6/1992 (Carton 6)
  - Invoice Records, Oct. 1975 - Dec. 2000 (Carton 6)
  - Money Receipt Book 1976-7 (Carton 6)
  - BSP Journal Ledger 1975-6 (Carton 6)
- Series IV. JOB FILES, CHRONOLOGICAL
  Listing generated from creator's folder title and entered by student assistants. Reverse chronological order. Many abbreviations remain, for example: GLA is Gleeson Library Associates.
  - Job files, late 1970s - early 1980s
    - Koch Logo Design, by Gene Holton, Santa Cruz, 1982/3? (Carton 7)
    - Experimental Papers for cover of Rettingruel (sp?) Black Stone Pess (Carton 7)
    - Black Stone Press Archive lists (Carton 7)
    - Mailing: Faurest Davis Portfolio, 1981 (Carton 7)
    - Black Stone Press, Ledger Pages, 1975-6 (Carton 7)
    - Center for Book Arts, #100 (Carton 7)
    - Deadstart, Issue 2, #101 (Carton 7)
    - Judith Shane Stat., #102 (Carton 7)
    - Wm. Stout Books, #103 (Carton 7)
    - "The Berkeley Graduate" design only, #104 (Carton 7)
    - Dirk Lee - "Alice Project" cancelled, #105 (Carton 7)
    - Jennings/Stout Arch., #106 (Carton 7)
    - 1061 Walker Ave. Stat., #109 (Carton 7)
    - Levinson Portfolio, #110 (Carton 7)
    - Peter Coyote Stat., #111 (Carton 7)
    - GLA 1980, #112 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 - GLA Kennedy Gifts Exhib. Annc., #113 (Carton 7)
    - A Trumpet of Our Own postcard annc., #114 (Carton 7)
    - MJ Brantsen citation, #115 (Carton 7)
    - Faurest Davis Portfolio Doc., #116 (Carton 7)
    - Stamets/Perez Wedding, #117 (Carton 7)
    - Cover for Architecture Cat., #118 (Carton 7)
    - Wm. Stout books BUSINESS CARDS, Gift Cert., and Stat., #119 (Carton 7)
    - GLA J.H. Nash Exhibit Annc., #120 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Clifford Burke Exhibit, #121 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Autumn Lecture, #122 (Carton 7)
    - A Trumpet of Our Own, #123 (Carton 7)
    - A Trumpet of Our Own, #123 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Writer Lecture Annc., #124 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Winter Meeting, #125 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Annual Mtg Keepsake, #126 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Annual mtg. annc., #127 (Carton 7)
    - GLA annual symposium - Dostoevsky, #128 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Teilhard de Chardin lecture, #129 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 GLA Spring Tour annc., #130 (Carton 7)
    - Ex librs Lilienthal/GLA bookplates, #131 (Carton 7)
    - Homage to Max Ernst, Wolf von den Bussche Portfolio, #132 (Carton 7)
    - Ex Libris H. Tyler (GL Donne Collection) 1982; #133 (Carton 7)
    - Bananas Hair Salon Opening (print only) 1982; #134 (Carton 7)
    - Joel Levinson Portfolio and Labels 1982; #135 (Carton 7)
    - Roxburghe Club--Keepsake 1982; #137 (Carton 7)
    - Peter Koch Stat., eps, BUSINESS CARDS 1982; #138 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Winter Mtg. Annc. 1982; #139 (Carton 7)
    - GLA California Dante Exhibit Reception Invitations 1982; #140 (Carton 7)
    - "The Voyage of the Raccoon" Book Club of California 1982; #141 (Carton 7)
    - USF Chinese Dinner Keepsake 1982; #142 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Anniversary Reception Announcements 1982; #143 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Christmas 1982; #144 (Carton 7)
    - Jennings and Stout Christmas Card 1983; #145 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Autumn Mtg Annc.- Rothenstein 1983; #146 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake 1983; #147 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Spring Tour Villa Montalvo [c] Annc. 1983; #148 (Carton 7)
    - Roxburghe Club- Mtg. Annc. 1983; #149 (Carton 7)
    - The Niantic Lithographic Stone (Rox. Club Keepsake) 1983; #150 (Carton 7)
    - Jeffrey Thomas Rare Books Stat and eps and BUSINESS CARDS 1983; #151 (Carton 7)
    - Cooper/ Ved Menta Wedding Annc. (printed for A. Wilson) 5 pc. 1983; #152 (Carton 7)
    - John B. Coll Books Catalog (not printed) 1983; #153 (Carton 7)
    - Stanley Marcus Proposals (not printed) 1983; #154 (Carton 7)
    - Niven Busch Estimate (not printed) 1983; #155 (Carton 7)
    - Orbis- Alan H. Cadgene BUSINESS CARDS 1983; #156 (Carton 7)
    - "Explanation of the Point System" Nelson Hawks, Kimble Collection of Western Printing History 1983; #157 (Carton 7)
    - Peter Coyote slat. 1983; #159 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Winter meeting- Victor Hammer Keepsake 1983; #160 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Annual Mtg. Annc. Dibner lecture 1983; #161 (Carton 7)
    - Rilke Poem Black Oak Books Broadside 1983; #162 (Carton 7)
    - "Short Cuts" BUSINESS CARDS 1983; #163 (Carton 7)
    - Peter Coyote Birth Annc and EP 1984; #164 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Rothenstein Exhibit Annc. Cards 1983; #167 (Carton 7)
    - Montana Gothic Poets Reading 1978; #826 (Carton 7)
    - Logon 83- Montana S. UnivP.Koch gave talk etitled "From the Crystal Goblet to Fast Food: Aspects of Technology Literacy" 1983; #828 (Carton 7)
    - Montana Arts Council (on which P. Koch served) 1983; #829 (Carton 7)
    - Jeffery Thomas Rare Books Cat. #1165 (Carton 7)
    - The Somniloquists Press- Bill Wolak #1163 (Carton 7)
    - Pacific Center for Book Arts 1980-81 #1164 (Carton 7)
    - Jeffery Thomas Annc. 1982; #1168 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Barkan Bookplate 1981; #1171 (Carton 7)
    - GLA Autumn Mtg Keepsake--Rothenstein 1983; #1172 (Carton 7)
    - Jennings Stout Arch. Stat. 1984; #165 (Carton 7)
    - Jennings Stout Arch. Stat. 1984; #166 (Carton 7)
    - Robert Hass Broadside Black Oak Books 1984; #191 (Carton 7)
    - "The Child I Was Before" Robert Duncan Broadside for Black Oak Books 1984; #192 (Carton 7)
    - Ramayana Book 1984; #193 (Carton 7)
    - Garrett Eckbo 1984; #194 (Carton 7)
    - Jennings Stout: Greeting Card 1984; #195 (Carton 7)
    - Jeanie Sack: Stationery 1984; #196 (Carton 7)
    - Allen Press 1984; #197 (Carton 7)
    - Harlan Kessel- VC Press Retirement 1984; #199 (Carton 7)
    - Pasch Wedding Invitation 1984; #200 (Carton 7)
    - Epes Ellery A Bookstore for Western Printing- Kimble Collections Keepsake 1984; #201 (Carton 7)
    - "Locate a Western" Koch/Roether 1984; #846 (Carton 7)
    - Exhibit Announcement for Robert Louis StevensonGleason Library 1984; #1173 (Carton 7)
    - 1982, Archive Sale to D. Belch; #796 (Carton 21)
    - 1982, Black Stone Press B.C.; #797 (Carton 21)
    - 1982, Moving to Montana; #798 (Carton 21)
    - 1982, To Wm Wreden - R.E. Sale of B. Stone Press Archive; #799 (Carton 21)
  - Job files, 1985
    - "Incantation" Czeslaw Milosv- Black Oak Books; #203 (Carton 8)
    - Egypt Poster for USF Summer Symposium; #204 (Carton 8)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography Publicity #206 (Carton 8)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography Stat. EP; #207 (Carton 8)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography Stickers; # 208 (Carton 8)
    - Roxburghe Club- Keepsake- H. Brunschwig; # 210 (Carton 8)
    - USF Bookplate; #211 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Christmas Card Greygnog Press Announcement; # 212 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting Announcement- "A Great Black Book"; # 213 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting Program- "A Great Black Book: Steinbecks East of Eden and Dr. Gunns Family Medicine"; #214 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Program- "The Pattern Designs of W. Morris"; # 215 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement- "W. Morris Designs"; #216 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Spring Tour- Steinbecks Cannery Row; # 217 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Program- Paul Horgan: A Collectors Choice; # 218 (Carton 8)
    - "The Depths- Denise Levertov for Black Oak Books; #219 (Carton 8)
    - Fernaut-Hartman Architects Stationery/envelopes; # 220 (Carton 8)
    - Gleeson Library- Prairie Press Exhibit; # 221 (Carton 8)
    - Book Club of CA- Rampant Lions Press Lecture #222 (Carton 8)
    - Childrens Medical Center- Medical Staff Room Opening; #223 (Carton 8)
    - Black Oak; #224 (Carton 8)
    - Weiner Memorial Service; #225 (Carton 8)
    - Foolish Compromise Book; #226 (Carton 8)
    - Nineteen Hundred and nineteen- Yeats Poem; # 228 (Carton 8)
    - Wolf van dem Bussche Portfolio; #229 (Carton 8)
    - International Association of Bibliophiles- San Francisco Program; #231 (Carton 8)
    - SFPL Book Club- Public Program; # 234 (Carton 8)
    - Roxsburghe Club- Keepsake Mundy Photographs; #236 (Carton 8)
    - Moomjian 50th Birthday Invite; # 1174 (Carton 8)
  - Job files, 1986
    - GLA Autumn Lecture Announcement (Oz); #238 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting Keepsake (Oz); #239 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Program; #240 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Spring Tour (Point Reyes Olema); # 241 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement- "Shakespeare, Lincoln Pestalozzi"; # 243 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Announcement- "Mountains and Books"; #244 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Keepsake; #245 (Carton 8)
    - Printers Portfolio- Roxburghe Club; #246 (Carton 8)
    - Wendell Berry Broadside "The Wild Rose" for Black Oak Books; # 247 (Carton 8)
    - "The Heart Asks Pleasure First" Emily Dickenson Book; #250 (Carton 8)
    - Publicity Announcement for rare books and manuscripts collections in Library of San Francisco Bay; # 251 (Carton 8)
    - George Fox Business Card- Gardner/ Fulmer Lithograph business card; # 252 (Carton 8)
    - The Jesuit School at Berkeley; #253 (Carton 8)
    - "Homage to Kertesz" W. van dem Bussche Portfolio; #254 (Carton 8)
    - Roxburghe Club- R. Jeffers Keepsake; # 256 (Carton 8)
    - Dugald Sterner Stationery/ business card; # 257 (Carton 8)
    - California Poets in the schools-broadside; #261 (Carton 8)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society-Broadside; #262 (Carton 8)
    - Roxburghe Club-Keepsake: Statue of Liberty; # 263 (Carton 8)
    - Klaus-Ullrich Roetzcher Birth Announcement; #264 (Carton 8)
    - B. Vorst Lecture Invitation for Boof Club of CA; # 265 (Carton 8)
    - Lorna Chan Stationery and Business Card; #266 (Carton 8)
    - Kutten Birth Announcement; #268 (Carton 8)
    - Backen. Arrigoni and Ross Architecture Announcement; #269 (Carton 8)
    - Jim Jennings Business Card and Stationery; #270 (Carton 8)
    - USF Summer Sympsosium- "Victory Through Suffering" (Carton 8)
    - Seventeen Street Studios- BUSINESS CARDS. Broadside Stationery; #276 (Carton 8)
    - Seventeenth Street Studios Christmas Print; #277 (Carton 8)
    - ARQ Stationery; #278 (Carton 8)
    - Scarab II- David Belch BUSINESS CARDS; # 279 (Carton 8)
    - Jim Jennings Christmas Card; # 280 (Carton 8)
    - Peter Coyote Stationery; # 281 (Carton 8)
    - Klaus- Ullrich S. Rotzschue Stationery; #282 (Carton 8)
    - Cook Book- Thomas Cook Achievements; #283 (Carton 8)
    - Conference on the Underrepresentaion of Minorities in the Medical and other health professions: Kaiser family Foundation; # 284 (Carton 8)
    - American Institution of Graphic Arts Exhibition; #830 (Carton 8)
  - Job files, 1987
    - "Trips" Magazine Cards (Stinehour Design); #288 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting (Sitwell) Program; #289 (Carton 8)
    - USF Symposium- "The Stranger"; #291 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Program (A.E. Housman); #292 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Winter Meeting- A.E. Housman Exhibit Announcement and E.P.; #293 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting (H.P. Roche) Program; # 295 (Carton 8)
    - GLA Annual Meeting (Henri-Pierre Roche) Announcement; #296 (Carton 8)
    - John de Pol Announcement- Book Club of CA; #298 (Carton 8)
    - Fernau and Hartman- Stationery. Eps, Business Cards, labels; # 299 (Carton 8)
    - Grimes/ Hogue Wedding Announcement- Eps, Reception Card, RSVP; #300 (Carton 8)
    - Steele/Kraut and Kraemer Birth Announcements and Eps.; #307 (Carton 8)
    - Book Club of California Anouncment; #302 (Carton 8)
    - Lotte Hellinga- Roxburghe Club Announcement; #303 (Carton 8)
    - Mimi Nielson Business Card; #304 (Carton 8)
    - Bigzig Video Ad; #305 (Carton 8)
    - CoLab Business System (Lonnie Graham Design): business card; envelopes, folder, stationery; #306 (Carton 8)
    - Roxburghe Club Announcements Robert Brophy on R. Jeffers; #307 (Carton 9)
    - Wood Science Lab- Stationery and Envelopes; #308 (Carton 9)
    - Logonet Envelopes; #309 (Carton 9)
    - Carol Newsom Design Stationery and eps; #310 (Carton 9)
    - M. karpilow Business cards; #315 (Carton 9)
    - A. Crawford/ Kenter Canyon Farms Stationery and EPS; #316 (Carton 9)